## Favour Abangwu

Front-End Developer

Frontend developer with demonstrated ability to work well with experienced developers while devoting extra time to be mentored. I like working closely with my teammates and picking up the slack when necessary. Ready to bring my coding passion to a talented engineering team in order to create high-quality solutions.

EXPERIENCE

Kwek Frontend Developer Nov 2021 - Present

- $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$  Developing features to enhance user experience .
- $\cdot$  Building stable and maintainable codebase using React.
- · Optimizing web pages for maximum efficiency.
- $\cdot$  Work closely with other team members on the development team.

HNG Internship 8 Frontend Developer Intern(Finalist) Aug 2021 - Oct 2021

Implemented the design for Zuri Channels Plugin to be utilized as social media platform for organizations on a large scale.

- Worked with designers to design, implement and host a channels game plugin.
- Collaborated with a team of frontend developers to implement the interface of a workspace.
- $\bullet \ \ Leveraging \ responsive \ web \ frameworks \ to \ complete \ deliverables \ ahead \ of \ schedule.$

Afen Group Frontend Developer Jun 2021 - Aug 2021

- Implemented the redesign of their website and landing pages from conception to deployment .
- Evaluated UI and UX designs for technical feasibility.
- Standardized user interfaces with a new responsive, mobile-first approach.

EDUCATION

Federal University of Technology, Owerri

B.Eng in Chemical Engineering

**Holberton School** 

Diploma in Software Engineering

AltSchool

Diploma in Frontend Engineering

References available on request

New Karu, Karu L.G.A., Nasarawa State. +234 9063652661 favourabangwu@gmail.com

SPECIALTIES

HTML, CSS

Tailwind CSS

SASS/SCSS

JavaScript

React

Chakra UI

GIT

Attention to detail

Highly organized

Teamwork